YUBAHWE SHEMA CHRISTIAN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



yubahwesc@gmail.com

kigali,Rwanda

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional software developer with 3 years of experience in software development. I have Strong eperience in backend engineer and frontend engineer skills. I am passionate about Technology and very interested in new ideas and new ways of thinking

SKILLS

- Nodejs
- Laravel
- React is
- Expressis
- Sequelizejs
- MongoDB & Postgresql
- React Native
- Web Design
- Nextis
- Typscript
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

GSSt Joseph Kabgayi

2016 - 2018

COMPUTER AND SOFTWARE ENGINEERING
University of Rwanda

2019-2023

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

eagle technology

2022 - 2023

- Leading Technology in Teck Stack
- Built the logic for a streamlined ad-serving platform that scaled
- Built Software System
- Search Engine Optimazation

BACKEND ENGINEER

solvit africa

2022(Feb-May)

• I worked as a backend software developer using node JS

FREELANCER SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

2019-2022

REFERNCE

CEO AT SOLVIT AFRICA

Joseph SEMAFARA

+250783137485

IT SUPPORT OFFICER AT INGABO HEALTH CENTER

gustave.muhoza@ingabo.rw

Software Engineer at Proqio Spain

✓ arsenemerci@proqio.com